import type { MCQ } from '../../../types'

export const mcqSet5: MCQ[] = [
  {
    "id": 36,
    "question": "A summary of a piece of writing or a paragraph is known as a ___.",
    "options": [
      "executive summary",
      "precis writing",
      "essay writing",
      "report writing"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 37,
    "question": "___ is used to let people know about certain facts or information.",
    "options": [
      "Informational notice",
      "legal notice",
      "public notice",
      "acknowledgement"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 38,
    "question": "___ planning is an essential component of successful business management.",
    "options": [
      "effective",
      "organisational",
      "powerful",
      "Business"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 39,
    "question": "A ___ is a form of business structure that comprises two or more owners.",
    "options": [
      "corporation",
      "sole proprietorship",
      "partnership",
      "LLC"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 40,
    "question": "In the film Breakfast Club, a group of teens are together for detention. One girl, Allison, seemingly self-discloses her bizarre sexual activity in an effort to get another teen, Claire, to disclose her sexual activity. Self-disclosing about oneself in an effort to get information from someone else may work because of which characteristic of self-disclosure?",
    "options": [
      "self-disclosure usually occurs in increments",
      "self-disclosure usually is reciprocal",
      "self-disclosure usually occurs in dyads",
      "all the above"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 41,
    "question": "Marcia decided to end her friendship with Ann, who was always cancelling plans at the last minute and borrowing money. This decision was likely based on ___.",
    "options": [
      "the social exchange theory",
      "self-clarification",
      "self-validation",
      "reciprocity"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 3
  },
  {
    "id": 42,
    "question": "The information that is known to you but unknown to others. Which quadrant is this?",
    "options": [
      "unknown",
      "hidden",
      "blindspot",
      "open"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 43,
    "question": "___ do not follow conventional rules.",
    "options": [
      "Progress report",
      "Formal meetings",
      "Informal meetings",
      "Executive meetings"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 44,
    "question": "If a report is written, based on personal enquiry or observations, then ___",
    "options": [
      "sentences should be in the second person and in direct speech.",
      "sentences should be in the third person and in direct speech.",
      "sentences should be in the first person and in direct speech.",
      "sentences should be in the first person and in indirect speech."
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 45,
    "question": "A good elevator pitch should last no longer ___.",
    "options": [
      "1 minute",
      "1 hour",
      "20 minutes",
      "20 seconds"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  }
]
